Finding Aid for League of Women Voters of the Ann Arbor Area records, 1920-2009
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
League of Women Voters of the Ann Arbor Area records
1920-2009
League of Women Voters of the Ann Arbor Area. Michigan Historical Collections staff
14.5 linear feet in 15 boxes
851657 Bm 2
Administrative and organizational records; files relating to elections and local and state issues.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The records came from the League (donor no. 5056 ) and from individual League officers in multiple accessions.
Periodic additions to the papers are expected.
The collection is open to research.
The early history of what is now known as the League of Women Voters of the Ann Arbor Area is uncertain. According to some accounts, this chapter of the League was first organized in 1920 as a by-product of the woman's suffrage movement. Meetings were held in the high school building. For much of the 1920s, however, except for an occasional speaker, the organization was inactive. In November 1934, the Ann Arbor chapter was reorganized and with approval of the state office the reorganized league chapter was given encouragement to act as a clearinghouse of governmental and political information to be taken to local civic organizations. Issues of concern to the league in these years included maternal health, child welfare, civil service reform, and problems arising out of the depression.
During the war years, the Ann Arbor League directed its energies toward the revision of the city's charter and the various activities that came to be known as Voter Service. To help the citizenry make informed choices, League members now began gathering and distributing information about the candidates running for local elections, about ballot proposals, and about legislation pending before the state legislature or the U.S. Congress.
In 1974, the Ann Arbor and Ypsilanti League chapters merged to form the League of Women Voters of the Ann Arbor Area. The purpose of the league today continues to be the promotion of political responsibility in government. Voter education remains its primary emphasis. As a nonpartisan group, the League does not take a position on political parties or candidates, only on issues, and only after its members have made a thorough study of the issue and reached consensus.
The records of the League of Women Voters of the Ann Arbor Area have been arranged into the following series: Organizational Records, 1942-1966 (mainly Mrs. Ivan Duff files); Health Care and Planning Issues, 1966-1973; Administrative, 1920-1990; Elections, 1946-1982; Issues, 1944-1981: and Topical files, 1969-1983. As the records came from different donors, there is some inevitable overlap between the various series.
Subjects:
Ann Arbor (Mich.); Ann Arbor (Mich.)--Charters.; Ann Arbor (Mich.)--Politics and government.; City planning--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; Elections--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; Hospitals--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; Michigan. Constitutional Convention (1961-1962); Municipal government--Michigan.; Public health--Michigan--Washtenaw County.; Taxation--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; Washtenaw County (Mich.); Women--Michigan--Ann Arbor--Societies and clubs.; Public schools--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; League of Women Voters of the Ann Arbor Area.
- Organizational records, 1942-1966
  The Organizational Records series were files accumulated by Mrs. Ivan Duff. Subject include the state constitutional convention of 1961-1962 and the revision of Ann Arbor's city charter as proposed, discussed, and realized in the period of 1948 to 1955.
  - Historical notes, 1954 (Box 1)
  - Papers (reports, clippings, memoranda, etc.)
    - Undated, 1942; 1946 (Box 1)
    - 1947, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - 1948 (Box 1)
    - 1949-1951 (Box 1)
    - 1952 (Box 1)
    - 1953 (Box 1)
    - 1954, 3 folders (Box 1)
    - 1955, 3 folders (Box 1)
    - 1956, 3 folders (Box 1)
    - 1957, 3 folders (Box 1)
    - 1958 (Box 1)
    - 1959, 3 folders (Box 1)
    - 1960-1963 (Box 1)
    - 1964, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 1)
  - City Charter Revision Files
    - Undated (Box 1)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 1)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 1)
    - 1953, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - 1954 (Box 1)
    - 1955, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Ann Arbor Public Schools Files, 1947-1959; 4 folders (Box 1)
  - Constitutional Convention File
    - Undated, 1958-1959 (Box 1)
    - 1960, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - 1961, 3 folders (Box 1)
    - 1962 (Box 1)
  - City Planning File
    - Undated, 1949 (Box 2)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 2)
    - 1954 (Box 2)
    - 1955-1957 (Box 2)
    - 1958 (Box 2)
    - 1959 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous File
    - Taxation (Box 2)
    - Voters Guides, 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Candidates interviews, 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Membership lists, 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Annexations (Box 2)
    - Ann Arbor Citizen's Council (Box 2)
- Health Care and Planning Issues, 1966-1973
  The Health Care and Planning Issues series consists primarily of reports, memoranda, and clippings relating to the status and reorganization of health care services in Washtenaw County in the period of 1966 to 1973. Some of the subjects covered in the files concern the controversy of the relocation of St. Joseph Mercy Hospital, family planning, medical services to the disadvantaged, and adult foster care homes.
  - Medical Care Resource Group Committee
    - Correspondence, 1969-1972; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Meetings, minutes, and resolutions, 1967-1972; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Membership and personnel, 1968-1973 (Box 2)
    - Reports and memos, 1966-1972; 4 folders (Box 2)
    - Interviews, 1967-1972 (Box 2)
    - Child health care services, 1966-1969 (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous (scattered dates) (Box 2)
  - Washtenaw County
    - Board of Commissioners reports, 1969-1972; 4 folders (Box 2)
    - Medical Care Study Committee reports, 1968-1969; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - County Hospital, Griffith report, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Board of Health (Box 2)
    - Agendas and meeting minutes, 1970-1972 (Box 2)
    - Reports and memos, 1969-1972 (Box 2)
    - Health Department (scattered dates) (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous (scattered dates) (Box 2)
  - Comprehensive Health Planning Council
    - Correspondence and notes, 1968-1972 (Box 2)
    - Reports and memos, 1966-1972; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Background material (scattered dates) (Box 3)
    - Clippings, 1968-1972 (Box 3)
    - Printed material, 1966-1972 (Box 3)
  - Ambulance Ordinance
    - Meeting agendas and notes, 1970-1971 (Box 3)
    - Reports and memos, 1967-1971 (Box 3)
    - Clippings, 1969-1972 (Box 3)
  - Family planning
    - Correspondence and notes, 1970-1971 (Box 3)
    - Reports and memos, 1970-1971 (Box 3)
    - Clippings, 1969-1970 (Box 3)
    - Printed material (scattered dates) (Box 3)
    - Planned Parenthood League, 1970-1971 (Box 3)
  - Medical care for the indigent
    - Reports and memos, 1966-1972; 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Printed material and clippings (scattered dates) (Box 3)
  - Dental services for the indigent, 1969-1972 (Box 3)
  - Adult Foster Care Permit Homes
    - Notes and memos, 1968-1971 (Box 3)
    - Committee notes and reports, 1969-1972 (Box 3)
    - Legislation, 1970-1972 (Box 3)
    - Grant proposal, "Senior Citizen Therapy and Day Care Center,", 1971 (Box 3)
    - Clippings, 1969-1973 (Box 3)
  - Nursing homes, 1966-1968; 1971 (Box 3)
  - Medical Committee for Human Rights, 1970-1972 (Box 3)
  - Model Cities, 1970 (Box 3)
  - Drug abuse, 1970-1971 (Box 3)
  - Health care, national issues (scattered dates), 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous (scattered dates) (Box 3)
  - Clippings largely concerning hospitals and health care, 1966-1973; 6 folders (Box 3)
- Administrative, 1920-1989
  The Administrative series (1920-1990) series includes runs of annual reports, board minutes, and the League's newsletter.
  - Annual meetings, 1951-1983; 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Annual meeting of Joint Board, 1969-1980 (Box 3)
  - Annual reports, 1944-1953 (Box 3)
  - Annual reports, (some gaps), 1954-1990; 5 folders (Box 4)
  - Annual reports to state office, (some gaps), 1947-1981; 3 folders (Box 4)
  - Annual reports of vice presidents, committees, etc., 1951-1978 (Box 4)
  - Annual reports of voters service unit, 1961-1970 (Box 4)
  - Audits, 1950-1977 (Box 4)
  - Board meetings, 1935-1950 (scattered) and 1971-1989, 8 folders (Box 4)
  - Treasurer's reports, (some gaps), 1980s; 3 folders (Box 5)
  - Budget notes, 1977 (Box 5)
  - Budget, proposed, (scattered), 1980-1984 (Box 5)
  - Budget (correspondence regarding), 1950-1969 (Box 5)
  - Bulletins, 1944-1989; 13 folders (Box 5)
  - By-laws, 1941-1988 (Box 5)
  - Community Action, 1947-1969 (Box 5)
  - Cooperation with other groups, 1950s-1960s (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, (scattered), 1970s-1980s (Box 5)
  - Duties of officers, 1967-1984 (Box 5)
  - Freedom Forum, 1954-1956 (Box 5)
  - Fund raising correspondence, 1950-1969, 1975-1989 (with gaps), 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Historical and background information, 1920-1982 (Box 6)
  - Letters for financial drive, 1948-1979 (Box 6)
  - Letters to representatives, 1977-1984 (Box 6)
  - Local program planning, 1976-1977 (Box 6)
  - Members lists, (some gaps), 1971-1989 (Box 6)
  - Membership coffees, 1964-1970 (Box 6)
  - Membership materials, 1978 (Box 6)
  - Merger with Ypsilanti LWV, 1973-1974; 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Monthly units, 1967-1969 (Box 6)
  - Office policies and procedures, (scattered), 1960-1986 (Box 6)
  - Phone call-in, 1972-1973 (Box 6)
  - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Policy and procedure, 1979-1989 (Box 6)
  - Political correspondence, 1974-1984 (Box 6)
  - Presidential letters, 1983-1984 (Box 6)
  - Program Record and Local Action, (scattered), 1963-1973 (Box 6)
  - Program workshop, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Questions on LWV procedures, 1945 (Box 6)
  - Radio and television, 1956-1957 (Box 6)
  - State conventions, 1979-1981; 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Unit material, 1968-1972 (Box 6)
- Elections
  The Elections series (1946-1982) contain the most complete file of materials relating to city elections - to the council, for mayor, the school board, ballot proposals, etc. This series includes voter's guide materials, clippings, and various informational files.
  - Absentee ballots, 1972-1976 (Box 6)
  - Ann Arbor city income tax relief, 1969 (Box 6)
  - Ballot proposals, 1969 (Box 6)
  - Candidates, 1968-1969 (Box 6)
  - Candidate Forums, 1961-1968 (Box 6)
  - Candidate interviews, 1948-1954 (Box 6)
  - Candidate meetings, 1959-1965; 3 folders (Box 6)
  - Candidate Nights, 1972-1977 (Box 6)
  - Candidate profiles, (scattered), 1950-1963 (Box 6)
  - Candidate questionnaires, 1973-1974 (Box 6)
  - Candidate surveys, 1950-1955 (Box 6)
  - City and county government elections, 1946-1972; 12 folders (Box 6)
  - City and county government elections, 1973-1979; 11 folders (Box 7)
  - Clippings (Box 7)
    (in oversize box 15)
  - Community college, 1965; 1972 undated (Box 7)
  - Constitutional Convention candidates, 1961 (Box 7)
  - County Board of Supervisors, 1949-1954 (Box 7)
  - Fair campaign practices, 1971 (Box 7)
  - Housing Commission special election, 1965 (Box 7)
  - Inter-School district election, 1971 (Box 7)
  - Key precinct reporting, 1976-1977 (Box 7)
  - School board and millage, 1949-1951; 1960-1965; 1970-1977; 12 folders (Box 7)
  - State and national, (scattered), 1946-1978; 8 folders (Box 7)
  - "They represent you,", 1948 (Box 7)
  - Voter's Guide, (scattered), 1950-1981 (Box 7)
    (see also oversize box 15)
  - Voter participation, 1980 (Box 7)
  - Voter registration, 1960-1975; 2 folders (Box 7)
  - "Your Government Officials,", 1965-1989; 3 folders (Box 7)
  - "Your vote counts,", 1953-1964 (Box 7)
- Issues
  The Issues series (1940-1981) is arranged alphabetically by topic.
  - Action Committee, 1973-1977 (Box 8)
  - Airport, (some gaps), 1975-1981 (Box 8)
  - Ann Arbor Citizens' Tax Committee, 1971 (Box 8)
  - Ann Arbor City Council, (with gaps), 1974-1984 (Box 8)
  - Ann Arbor Public Schools, (with gaps), 1969-1985 (Box 8)
  - Annexation of East Ann Arbor, 1956 (Box 8)
  - Area planning goals, 1954-1967 (Box 8)
  - Board of Education/Program Action, 1971-1976 (Box 8)
  - Bond issues, 1966 (Box 8)
  - Budget and financing of city of Ann Arbor, 1968-1971 (Box 8)
  - Campaign financing, 1973-1974 (Box 8)
  - Capital Improvements Program, 1954-1977 (Box 8)
  - Charter Commission, 1952-1954 (Box 8)
  - Charter revision, 1947-1955 (Box 8)
  - Citizen's view, 1952 (Box 8)
  - City government, 1952-1967 (Box 8)
  - City income tax, 1969 (Box 8)
  - City litigation, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - Civil rights, 1971-1979; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Clean air, 1970-1975 (Box 8)
  - Congressional reform, 1971 (Box 8)
  - County assessor (property tax), 1966-1970 (Box 8)
  - County courthouse, 1949-1952 (Box 8)
  - County government, 1944-1950 (Box 8)
  - County government, 1969 (Box 8)
  - County home rule, 1964-1970 (Box 8)
  - Dependence dilemma conference (re gasoline consumption), 1981 (Box 8)
  - Discussion, 1962 (Box 8)
  - Education, 1949-1961; 1972-1977; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Education Fund, 1978-1981 (Box 8)
  - Education-State taxation, 1967-1969 (Box 8)
  - Election laws, 1976-1977 (Box 8)
  - Energy, 1974-1979 (Box 8)
  - Environment, 1973 (Box 9)
  - Environmental quality, 1970-1974 (Box 9)
  - Environmental quality (correspondence), 1973-1975 (Box 9)
  - Environmental quality newsletter and handbook, 1970-1971 (Box 9)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, 1972-1979 (Box 9)
  - Esch, Marvin (Congressman), 1968-1969; 1973 (Box 9)
  - Fair housing, 1962-1965 (Box 9)
  - Family and children's services, 1973-1979 (Box 9)
  - Financing city government, 1972-1973 (Box 9)
  - Financing local government, 1972-1975; 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Graduated income tax, 1967-1968 (Box 9)
  - Health, 1940-1950 (Box 9)
  - Housing, 1970-1979 (Box 9)
  - Housing, low-income, (chiefly 1966-1967), 1960-1971 (Box 9)
  - Housing (clippings), 1967-1968 (Box 9)
  - Housing Office, 1965-1967 (Box 9)
  - Housing referendum, 1965 (Box 9)
  - Human Relations Commission, 1959-1969; 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Human resources, 1970-1971 (Box 9)
  - Human Rights Commission/ordinance, 1966-1970 (Box 9)
  - Huron River Watershed Council, 1958-1968; 2 folders (Box 9)
  - In the Public Interest, 1973-1976 (Box 9)
  - Incentives for 21 year olds, 1951 (Box 9)
  - Individual liberties, 1950-1956 (Box 9)
  - International relations, 1976 (Box 9)
  - Juvenile delinquency, 1952-1957; 1984; 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Lake Erie Basin, (with gaps), 1962-1978; 3 folders (Box 10)
  - Land use (Michigan), 1974-1979 (Box 10)
  - Leadership materials, 1973-1975 (Box 10)
  - League statements-Hearings, 1973-1981 (Box 10)
  - Legislative correspondence, 1952-1965; 1973-1974; 3 folders (Box 10)
  - Local government, 1948-1953 (Box 10)
  - Medical care-Action and correspondence (Box 10)
  - Medical care committee, 1967-1973 (Box 10)
  - Miscellaneous, 1952-1965; 1969-1977; 3 folders (Box 10)
  - Model Cities, 1969 (Box 10)
  - Model Cities Election, 1971 (Box 10)
  - Municipal Court, 1947-1950 (Box 10)
  - Natural Beauty and Planning, 1963-1966 (Box 10)
  - Natural Rivers (Box 10)
  - Observer guidelines, 1967 (Box 10)
  - Observer program, 1975-1984 (Box 10)
  - Open meetings lawsuit, 1978 (Box 10)
  - Parks, 1962-1967; 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Parks and recreation, 1971 (Box 10)
  - Planning, (scattered dates), 1950-1978; 5 folders (Box 10)
  - Planning-Briarwood Center, 1966-1971 (Box 11)
  - Presidential powers, 1975-1977 (Box 11)
  - Program Action, 1970-1980 (Box 11)
  - Program making, 1971-1978 (Box 11)
  - Program suggestions, 1978-1979 (Box 11)
  - Project '74 (abandoned, delinquent and neglected children), 1966 (Box 11)
  - Public hearings, 1967-1969 (Box 11)
  - Public schools, 1955-1974 (Box 11)
  - Public statements, 1962-1967 (Box 11)
  - Punchcard voting, 1977-1979 (Box 11)
  - Racial imbalance, 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Radio and television, 1950-1954 (Box 11)
  - Registration drive, 1964 (Box 11)
  - Related organizations, 1958 (Box 11)
  - Rent control, 1974 (Box 11)
  - Shorelands, 1974-1976 (Box 11)
  - Sign ordinances, 1967-1968 (Box 11)
  - Special education, 1970 (Box 11)
  - State government programs, 1973-1977 (Box 11)
  - State taxation, 1945-1980; 4 folders (Box 11)
  - Statements, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Taxation, 1951-1953 (Box 11)
  - Third parties, 1971 (Box 11)
  - Town talks, 1957 (Box 11)
  - Transportation study, 1979-1985 (Box 11)
  - United Nations, 1976-1984; 1992-1995; 2003 (Box 11)
  - Urban crisis, 1978 (Box 11)
  - Urban renewal, 1956-1961; 2 folders (Box 11)
  - Washtenaw Intermediate School District, 1973 (Box 11)
  - Water quality, 1970-1979 (Box 11)
  - Water/sewage treatment, 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Zoning, 1956-1962; 1964; 2 folders (Box 11)
- Topical files (various officers), 1969-1983
  The Topical files series (1969-1983) represents an accumulation of records from different LWV officers. The bulk of the files relate to the litigation of the League against the city of Ann Arbor and the Ann Arbor Transportation Authority over alleged misuse of AATA funds.
  - Ann Arbor city annexation policy (general) and relating to Smokler--Murphy property, 1970-1974 (Box 12)
  - Ann Arbor Transportation Authority litigation, 1974-1975; 5 folders (Box 12)
  - Election law, 1975-1976 (Box 12)
  - Huron River and water resources, 1969-1972 (Box 12)
  - Land use, 1973; undated (Box 12)
  - Membership handbooks, 1972/1973-1975/1976 (Box 12)
  - Memoranda, statements, reports, etc., 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Publicity, 1972-1983 (Box 12)
  - Solid and hazardous waste, 1973, 1982-1989 (scattered) and undated (Box 12)
  - State program planning, 1969-1974 (Box 12)
  - United States Congress (consensus on reform of Congress), 1970-1971; undated (Box 12)
- Publications
  The Publications series contains titles on various topics published by the League between 1943 and 2009.
  - "Ann Arbor city government,", 1943 (Box 12)
  - "Did you know?", 1950-1956 (Box 12)
  - "Know your city,", 1977; 1986; 2 folders (Box 12)
  - "Know your county,", 1956; 1959; 1984 (Box 12)
  - "Know your schools,", 1955; 1957; 1969; 1974; 1984 (Box 12)
  - "Know your town,", 1953; 1963; 1966-1967; 3 folders (Box 12)
  - Newsletter, 1990-1997; 1999-2009; 5 folders (Box 12)
  - "A Study of the League of Women Voters of the United States,", 1956-1957 (Box 12)
- Materials dated after, 1990
  The Materials dated after 1990 series contains five subseries: Administrative files (by-laws, agenda and minutes of meetings, reports, lists of members and membership materials, and the League of Women Voters of the Ann Arbor Area correspondence); Activities (memoranda and correspondence related to specific events and programs); Elections (voter service materials and information, correspondence and memoranda, material related to the topic of national, state, and local elections, and photographs); Issues (reports, articles, correspondence and memoranda related to topics and issues of the day, arranged alphabetically); and Electronic materials (four 31/2-inch floppy disks, 2 CD-ROMs and 2 DVDs with reports, educational and promotional materials, dated between 1997 and 2009).
  - Administrative files
    - By-laws and policies, 1992-2008 (Box 13)
    - Officers, 1990-2009 (Box 13)
    - Board meetings agenda and minutes, 1990-2009; 4 folders (Box 13)
    - Annual reports, 1990/1991-2008/2009 with gaps, 3 folders (Box 13)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1992-2009; 5 folders (Box 13)
    - Pfizer grants, 2003-2005 (Box 13)
    - Correspondence, 1990-2009; 3 folders (Box 13)
    - Members lists, 1991-1999; 2001-2009; 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Membership materials, scattered, 1995-2008 (Box 13)
    - Ann Arbor Women's City Club, scattered, 1993-2003 (Box 13)
  - Activities
    - 75th Anniversary, 1995 (Box 13)
    - Program planning, scattered, 1990-2009 (Box 13)
    - Board Fellowship program, 2003-2005 (Box 13)
    - International visitors, 2003-2006 (Box 13)
    - State and national conventions, with gaps, 2003-2009 (Box 13)
    - People Speak, 2004 (Box 13)
    - Eastern Michigan University, 2004 (Box 13)
    - 21st Century Voter conference, 2009 (Box 13)
    - Various, scattered, 2000-2008 (Box 13)
  - Elections (Box 14)
    - "Your Elected Officials," with gaps, 1990-2010 (Box 14)
    - Voter guides and information, with gaps, 1990-2000; 3 folders (Box 14)
    - Voter service, 1991-2004; 2006-2010; 8 folders (Box 14)
    - Redistricting, 2005 (Box 14)
    - National popular vote, 2008-2009 (Box 14)
    - Photographs, 2002-2004 (Box 14)
  - Issues
    - Affirmative action, 2005-2007 (Box 14)
    - Cable service, 2008-2009 (Box 14)
    - Immigration, 2007-2008 (Box 14)
    - Judicial system, 2002; 2004; 2007-2008; 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Local governance, 2007-2008 (Box 14)
    - Natural resources, scattered, 1991-2007 (Box 14)
    - Physician's aid in dying, 1996-1999; 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 14)
  - Electronic materials
    - Annual report, 1997; 1 floppy disks 3.5" (Box 14)
    - Annual report, 2000; 1 floppy disks 3.5" (Box 14)
    - YEO brochure, 2000; 1 floppy disks 3.5" (Box 14)
    - Final draft letter to accompany YEOs, 2003; 1 floppy disks 3.5" (Box 14)
    - League of Women Voters of the Ann Arbor Area minutes, 1997-2009; 1 optical disks CD-ROMs (Box 14)
    - "85th anniversary making democracy work,", 2005; 1 optical disks DVD-Rs (Box 14)
    - "Affirmative action: access and opportunity,", undated; 1 optical disks CD-ROMs (Box 14)
    - "The 21st century voter: promoting Michigan voter power,", 1 optical disks DVD-Rs (Box 14)
- Tributes and commemorative resolution
  Lastly, there is a small series consisting of a special tribute award certificates and a commemorative resolution received by the League for its work.
  - Special tributes to the League from the State of Michigan, 1990; 1995; 2005 (Box 15)
  - Commemorating resolution from the Michigan House of Representatives, 1980 (Box 15)